So now we're finally ready to get our hands into training a neural network.
现在我们可以开始训练神经网络了
So let's quickly recall feedforward.
我们快速回顾一下前馈的概念
We have our perceptron with a point coming in labeled positive.
我们有一个感知器 其中有一个标签为正的输入点
And our equation w1x1 + w2x2 + b,
感知器的方程是 w1x1 + w2x2 + b
where w1 and w2 are the weights and b is the bias.
其中 w1 和 w2 是权重 b 是偏差
Now, what the perceptron does is,
感知器给出一个点
it plots a point and returns a probability that the point is blue.
返回该点是蓝色的概率
Which in this case is small since the point is in the red area.
这个例子中的概率比较小 因为该点位于红色区域
Thus, this is a bad perceptron since it
因此 这是个不太理想的感知器
predicts that the point is red when the point is really blue.
因为它预测该点是红色 但实际上该点是蓝色
And now let's recall what we did in the gradient descent algorithm.
我们回忆下我们在梯度下降算法中的做法
We did this thing called Backpropagation.
我们执行了一种被称为反向传播的操作
We went in the opposite direction.
我们朝着相反的方向前进
We asked the point, "What do you want the model to do for you?"
我们问这个点 “你需要模型为你做什么”
And the point says, "Well,
点回答说
I am misclassified so I want this boundary to come closer to me."
“我被错误分类了 我想让分类的边界离我近点”
And we saw that the line got closer to it by updating the weights.
我们看到直线通过更新权重 离它更近了
Namely, in this case,
在此情况下
let's say that it tells the weight w1 to go lower and the weight w2 to go higher.
我们假设它告诉权重 w1 变小些 权重 w2 变大些
And this is just an illustration,
当然这只是一个演示
it's not meant to be exact.
真实情况不一定是这样
So we obtain new weights,
我们得到新的权重
w1' and w2' which define a new line which is now closer to the point.
w1’ 和 w2’ 定义了一条新的直线 它现在离点更近了
So what we're doing is like descending from
我们的做法就像从误差之巅下来
Mt. Errorest, right?
对吧？
The height is going to be the error function E(W) and we calculate the gradient
高度将是误差函数 E(W)
of the error function which is exactly
我们计算误差函数的梯度
like asking the point what does is it want the model to do.
就像在问点希望模型做什么
And as we take the step down the direction of the negative of the gradient,
当我们朝着梯度的相反方向下山
we decrease the error to come down the mountain.
我们就减小了误差 从山上下来
This gives us a new error,
这样就得到了新的误差 E(W’)
E(W') and a new model W' with a smaller error,
以及一个误差更小的新模型 W’
which means we get a new line closer to the point.
意味着我们得到了离点更近的新直线
We continue doing this process in order to minimize the error.
我们继续这一流程 以最小化误差
So that was for a single perceptron.
这就是单个感知器的反向传播过程
Now, what do we do for multi-layer perceptrons?
对于多层级感知器 应该如何进行操作呢？
Well, we still do the same process of reducing the error by descending from the mountain,
我们依然通过相同的流程来减小误差并从山上下来
except now, since the error function is more complicated then it's not
但是现在误差函数更为复杂
Mt. Errorest, now it's
更像是乞力马扎罗山
Mt. Kilimanjerror. But same thing,
不再是简单的误差之巅
we calculate the error function and its gradient.
我们计算误差函数和它的梯度
We then walk in the direction of the negative of the gradient in order to find
然后朝着梯度的相反方向前进
a new model W' with a smaller error
以便找到新的模型
E(W') which will give us a better prediction.
它的误差函数 E(W’) 更小 会为我们提供更准确的预测
And we continue doing this process in order to minimize the error.
我们持续这一流程 以便最小化误差
So let's look again at what feedforward does in a multi-layer perceptron.
我们再看看多层级感知器中的前向反馈
The point comes in with coordinates (x1, x2) and label y = 1.
传入点的坐标是 (x1,x2) 标签是 y = 1
It gets plotted in the linear models corresponding to the hidden layer.
它对应的是隐藏层的线性模型
And then, as this layer gets combined the point gets
然后通过层级间的结合
plotted in the resulting non-linear model in the output layer.
这个点的最终结果通过整个非线性模型的输出层得到
And the probability that the point is blue is obtained by
该点是蓝色的概率等于
the position of this point in the final model.
该点在最终模型中的位置
Now, pay close attention because this is
现在请集中注意力
the key for training neural networks, it's Backpropagation.
因为这是训练神经网络的关键 我们讲到反向传播了
We'll do as before, we'll check the error.
和之前一样 查看一下这个模型得到的误差
So this model is not good because it predicts that
这个模型不太好 因为它预测这个点是红色
the point will be red when in reality the point is blue.
但实际上这个点是蓝色
So we'll ask the point,
我们问该点
"What do you want this model to do in order for you to be better classified?"
“为了分类正确 你希望该模型怎么做？”
And the point says, "I kind of want this blue region to come closer to me."
这个点说“我希望这个蓝色区域离我近点”
Now, what does it mean for the region to come closer to it?
让蓝色区域靠近点是什么意思？
Well, let's look at the two linear models in the hidden layer.
我们看看隐藏层中的两个线性模型
Which one of these two models is doing better?
哪个模型效果更好？
Well, it seems like the top one is badly misclassifying
似乎上面这个模型的分类结果很糟糕
the point whereas the bottom one is classifying it correctly.
而下面的模型分类正确
So we kind of want to listen to the bottom one more and to the top one less.
所以我们希望来自下面这个模型的影响增大 来自上面这个模型的影响缩小
So what we want to do is to reduce the weight coming from
我们要做的是减小来自上面这个模型的权重
the top model and increase the weight coming from the bottom model.
并增大来自下面这个模型的权重
So now our final model will look a lot
那么我们得到的模型看起来
more like the bottom model than like the top model.
更像下面的模型 而不是上面的模型
But we can do even more.
我们可以更加深入地解释
We can actually go to the linear models and ask the point,
我们可以从各个线性模型出发 问这个点
"What can these models do to classify you better?"
“为了更好地对你进行分类 这些模型应该怎么做？”
And the point will say, "Well,
该点说
the top model is misclassifying me,
“上面这个模型对我的分类不正确
so I kind of want this line to move closer to me.
我想这条线离我近些
And the second model is correctly classifying me,
第二个模型对我的分类正确
so I want this line to move farther away from me."
所以我想这条线离我远点”
And so this change in the model will actually update the weights.
模型据此更新权重
Let's say, it'll increase these two and decrease these two.
假设它将增大这两个权重 并减小那两个权重
So now after we update all the weights we have better predictions at
在更新了所有权重后
all the models in the hidden layer and
隐藏层中所有模型的预测更加准确
also a better prediction at the model in the output layer.
输出层中模型的预测也更为准确
Notice that in this video we intentionally left the bias unit away for clarity.
注意 在这个视频中 为了解释得更加清楚 我们故意省略了偏差
In reality, when you update the weights we're also updating the bias unit.
在现实中 当你更新权重时 你也会更新偏差单位
If you're the kind of person who likes formality,
如果你喜欢更为严谨的解释
don't worry, we'll calculate these gradients in detail soon.
别担心 我们稍后将详细地计算所有梯度